(Sheldon:)All right, I'm ready
for my next question.
(Amy:)In a world where rhinoceroses
are domesticated pets,
(Amy:)who wins the Second World War?
(Sheldon:)Uganda.
(Amy:)Defend.
(Sheldon:)Kenya rises to power
(Sheldon:)on the export of rhinoceroses.
(Sheldon:)A Central African
power block is formed,
(Sheldon:)colonizing North Africa and Europe.
(Sheldon:)When war breaks out, no one can
afford the luxury of a rhino.
(Sheldon:)Kenya withers, Uganda triumphs.
(Amy:)Correct.
(Amy:)My turn.
(Sheldon:)In a world where a piano is a weapon,
not a musical instrument,
(Sheldon:)on what does Scott Joplin
play "The Maple Leaf Rag"?
(Amy:)Tuned bayonets.
(Amy:)Defend.
(Amy:)Isn't it obvious?
(Sheldon:)You're right. My apologies.
(Leonard:)What the hell are you guys playing?
(Sheldon:)It's a game we invented.
(Sheldon:)It's called Counterfactuals.